export const STORAGE_KEY = 'de_decks';

export const defaultDecks = [
  {
    id: 'deck-1',
    name: 'Немецкий — базовый',
    cards: [
      { front: 'das Haus', back: 'дом' },
      { front: 'die Straße', back: 'улица' },
      { front: 'der Freund', back: 'друг' },
      { front: 'die Zeit', back: 'время' },
      { front: 'die Größe', back: 'размер' },
      { front: 'für immer', back: 'навсегда' },
      { front: 'schön', back: 'красивый' },
      { front: 'grün', back: 'зелёный' },
      { front: 'groß', back: 'большой' },
      { front: 'Fuß', back: 'нога, ступня' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'deck-2',
    name: 'Немецкий — two',
    cards: [
      { front: 'das Haus', back: 'дом' },
      { front: 'die Straße', back: 'улица' },
      { front: 'der Freund', back: 'друг' },
      { front: 'die Zeit', back: 'время' },
      { front: 'die Größe', back: 'размер' },
      { front: 'für immer', back: 'навсегда' },
      { front: 'schön', back: 'красивый' },
      { front: 'grün', back: 'зелёный' },
      { front: 'groß', back: 'большой' },
      { front: 'Fuß', back: 'нога, ступня' },
    ],
  }
];
